teamrankings.com 2007-12-14

# Privacy Policy : TeamRankings.com

| 

### TeamRankings.com Privacy Policy 

###### _Effective Date: October 11, 2005_

**1\. WHAT THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVERS**

Team Rankings, LLC (�Team Rankings�) takes the protection of your privacy very seriously. This policy covers how Team Rankings treats personal information about you that Team Rankings collects and receives, including information related to your use of Team Rankings products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable, like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Team Rankings does not own or control, or to people that Team Rankings does not directly employ or manage. 

**2\. INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE**

Team Rankings collects personal information when you register for access to certain services, when you use certain Team Rankings products or services, when you visit web pages on the TeamRankings.com web site or the web pages of certain Team Rankings partners, when you sign up for or respond to email newsletters or other free services, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes sponsored by Team Rankings. Team Rankings may combine information about you that we obtain directly with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. 

At certain times, we ask for information that may include, but is not limited to, your name, email address, mailing address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, and personal interests. Furthermore, once you register with Team Rankings and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. Team Rankings automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Team Rankings cookie information, and the page you request. Team Rankings also collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our advertisers and/or business partners, including information about your use of products and services that we offer. 

Team Rankings uses information collected about you to customize the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for products and services, to improve the quality and relevance of our services, to contact you, to conduct research, and to provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

**3\. INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE**

Team Rankings does not rent or sell your personal information to other people or nonaffiliated companies (or share your personal information with other people or nonaffiliated companies) except to provide products or services you've requested, either when we have your permission or under the following circumstances: 

a. We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Team Rankings under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Team Rankings communicate with you about offers from Team Rankings and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 

b. We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. 

c. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Team Rankings's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. 

d. We transfer information about you if Team Rankings is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Team Rankings will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

Team Rankings displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria (for example, men aged 35-44 from a particular geographic area). Team Rankings does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. 

**4\. COOKIES**

Team Rankings may set and access Team Rankings cookies on your computer. Team Rankings also lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Team Rankings's cookies. Team Rankings also uses web beacons to access Team Rankings cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with Team Rankings products and services. 

**5\. YOUR ABILITY TO EDIT AND DELETE YOUR ACCOUNT INFORMATION AND PREFERENCES**

You can change your Team Rankings account information (including your name, account username, account password, and email address) at any time by emailing [support@teamrankings.com ](mailto:support@teamrankings.com). You may also opt-out of any future marketing-related communications by emailing [support@teamrankings.com ](mailto:support@teamrankings.com) and notifying us of your desire to be removed from our marketing mailing lists. Team Rankings will make all reasonable efforts to process requested changes in your marketing preferences or account information within 72 hours of the receipt of your email request. 

We reserve the right to send you certain communications related to Team Rankings products and services, such as service announcements and administrative messages, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. 

You can terminate your Team Rankings account at any time by emailing [support@teamrankings.com ](mailto:support@teamrankings.com) and notifying us that you would like to terminate your account. Team Rankings will make all reasonable efforts to process account termination requests within 24 hours of the receipt of your email request. After your account is terminated, some information about you may remain in our archived records. 

**6\. CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY**

We limit access to personal information about you to employees and/or independent contractors under confidentiality agreements who we believe have a reasonable need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. We also employ a variety of procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you. While none of these safeguards represents a foolproof means of protecting your personal information from unauthorized access, we take very seriously the protection of your privacy. 

**7\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

Team Rankings may update this policy from time to time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Team Rankings account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

**8\. QUESTIONS AND SUGGESTIONS**

If you have questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please email us at [support@teamrankings.com ](mailto:support@teamrankings.com). 

|   
  
Copyright 2000-2007 Team Rankings, LLC. All rights reserved. All content on this site is produced for entertainment purposes only and is not intended to be used in direct or indirect violation of any local, state, federal, or international law(s). By using this site, you agree and consent to our [Terms of Service](http://teamrankings.com/tos.php) and [Privacy Policy](http://teamrankings.com/privacy.php).
